<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Media List</string>
    <string name="title_movie_detail">Media Detail</string>


    <!--    CS315: DO THIS-->
    <!--    TODO: Create five NEW movie objects here. Complete with images and URLs. DELETE the two existing movies, they are only here as an example-->

    <string name="tvshow_1">NCIS</string>
    <string name="tvshow_1_desc">Naval Criminal Investigative Service Special Agent Leroy Jethro Gibbs leads a group of colorful personalities in investigating crimes -- ranging from murder and espionage to terrorism -- that have evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_1_year">2003</string>
    <string name="tvshow_1_image">ncis</string>
    <string name="tvshow_1_url">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0364845/</string>

    <string name="tvshow_2">Chicago Fire</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2_desc">As the firefighters, rescue squad and paramedics of Chicago Firehouse 51 forge headfirst into danger, the choices they make can mean the difference between life and death. But from the relentless pressure of saving lives, an extended family is forged.</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2_year">2012</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2_image">fire</string>
    <string name="tvshow_2_url">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt2261391/</string>

    <string name="tvshow_3">Chicago PD</string>
    <string name="tvshow_3_desc">District 21 of the Chicago Police Department is composed of the uniformed cops, who deal with street crimes, and the Intelligence Unit, which deals with major crimes like drug trafficking and high-profile murders. Sgt Hank Voight - a tough boss who doesn't mind bending the rules a little</string>
    <string name="tvshow_3_year">2014</string>
    <string name="tvshow_3_image">pd</string>
    <string name="tvshow_3_url">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt2805096/</string>

    <string name="movie2">Martian</string>
    <string name="movie2_desc">When astronauts blast off from the planet Mars, they leave behind Mark Watney (Matt Damon), presumed dead after a fierce storm. With only a meager amount of supplies, the stranded visitor must utilize his wits and spirit to find a way to survive on the hostile planet.</string>
    <string name="movie2_year">2015</string>
    <string name="movie2_image">martian</string>
    <string name="movie2_url">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt3659388/</string>

    <string name="movie1">DeepWater Horizon</string>
    <string name="movie1_desc">On April 20, 2010, the Deepwater Horizon drilling rig explodes in the Gulf of Mexico, igniting a massive fireball that kills several crew members. Chief electronics technician Mike Williams (Mark Wahlberg) and his colleagues find themselves fighting for survival</string>
    <string name="movie1_year">2016</string>
    <string name="movie1_image">water</string>
    <string name="movie1_url">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1860357/</string>


</resources>
